

let questions = [
  {
      numb:1,
      question:'Which of the following language is MongoDB written in?',
      answer:'All of the mentioned',
      options:[
          "Javascript",
          "C",
          "C++",
          "All of the mentioned"
      ]
  },
  {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which of the following format is supported by MongoDB?",
      answer: "BSON",
      options: [
        "SQL",
        "XML",
        "BSON",
        "All of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "MongoDB stores all documents in",
      answer: "collections",
      options: [
        "tables",
        "collections",
        "rows",
        "all of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
  
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "MongoDB process collection of documents using _________ operations.",
      answer: "Map-reduce",
      options: [
        "Hbase",
        "Hive",
        "Map-reduce",
        "all of the mentioned"
      ]
    },

    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Capped collections provide __________ management of inserted documents in MongoDB.",
      answer: "FIFO",
      options: [
        "FIFO",
        "LIFO",
        "LRU",
        "MRU"
      ]
    },

    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "BSON is a binary representation of ________ documents.",
      answer: "JSON",
      options: [
        "XML",
        "JSON",
        "Javascript",
        "All of the mentioned"
      ]
    },

    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "MongoDB documents are composed of field-and-value pairs and have the following structure?",
      answer: "field1: value1;",
      options: [
        "field1:; value1",
        "field1: value1;",
        "field1: value1",
        "none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },

    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "When inserts, updates and deletes have a _________ write concern, write operations return quickly.",
      answer: "weak",
      options: [
        "strong",
        "weak",
        "average",
        "very strong"
      ]
    },

    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "The order of documents returned by a query is not defined unless you specify a ",
      answer: "sort()",
      options: [
        "sortfind()",
        "sortelse()",
        "sort()",
        "none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },

    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of the following method returns one document?",
      answer: "findOne()",
      options: [
        "findOne()",
        "findOne1()",
        "selectOne()",
        "all of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    
]
